Speaker: Tim Powell isn’t a morning person.
Which is surprising, because on weekdays he gets up very early.
While most of us are still asleep, Powell wakes up at 5.45,
does exercise for 30 minutes in his home gym, and has a big breakfast.
Then he gets ready for work and drives to the office.
When he gets to the building where he works, he goes for a walk around a local park,
then he goes inside to start work at 9.
And on Thursdays he gets up even earlier, at 5.20 a.m., to study German.
Powell is a lawyer.
He works 70 hours a week, and he says that getting up early helps him to do more during the day.
He isn’t the only one – many busy, successful people get up very early.